{
    "id": "9a7da5dbd0f64111869bb7f69e2c6fac",
    "title": "Personal Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Jack, Peter and Mary work at a call center. ………………….. are very industrious.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "They",
                "We",
                "You"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ece22b29461b4363be44a0b2a6b90abe"
        },
        {
            "question": "My sister and I like films. ………………… watch as many films as possible.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "We",
                "They",
                "You"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f6b2b4e1131434ca80bd531d6266750"
        },
        {
            "question": "On my birthday Peter gave ………………… a watch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "us",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a01090d8365045d58011904f0500d96b"
        },
        {
            "question": "On …………………. birthday I gave him a shirt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "his",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d250675052014bac83dd07fe1301c273"
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie sings really well. ……………….. has a golden voice.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "She",
                "He",
                "You"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ea02c6791b58481887a65004c070126e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Albert is in the national football team. …………………. is a good striker.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "He",
                "She",
                "It"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "494483d707bb4b799fc72d11f7022986"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tom and Brad are my favorite actors. I like ………………… very much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "those"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "76105747d4284f2fa38ce5d1325c30df"
        },
        {
            "question": "The elephant has a long trunk. ................................... has also got large ears.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "She",
                "He",
                "It"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c30c0831ef0545e59f208dd4ed48f2b5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The spider is an insect. ................................. has eight legs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "It",
                "He",
                "She"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a2fae32ed7d14b3ea93dec0d18001e9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The birds have made several nests on the branches. The nests have baby birds in ...............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them",
                "their"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "df3767bcb1eb4b2aa65b075b04b344c4"
        }
    ]
}